Center for Traditional Music and Dance collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
Center for Traditional Music and Dance collection 1968-2015 (bulk 1974-2011)
AFC 2014/044
Center for Traditional Music and Dance (New York, N.Y.)
13,551 items.
manuscripts 4,000 items.
525 photographic prints.
604 image files: digital; jpg, tif.
340 sound tape reels (7 in., 10 in.): analog.
277 sound discs (CD): digital; 4 3/4 in.
212 sound cassettes (DAT): digital.
6 sound cassettes (U-matic audio): digital.
4,171 audio files: digital; wav, mp3.
114 videotape reels (5 in., 7 in.): analog.
272 videocassettes (U-matic video): analog.
195 videocassettes (Betacam): analog.
24 videocassettes (Betacam SP): analog.
172 videocassettes (Betamax): analog.
43 videocassettes (VHS): analog.
373 videocassettes (MiniDV): digital.
97 videocassettes (DVCAM): digital.
10 video discs (DVD): digital; 4 3/4 in.
2,116 video files: digital; mts, m4v, mp4, mov, avi.
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress Washington, D.C.
Audio and video recordings, photographs, posters, and handouts related to programming by the Center for Traditional Music and Dance (CTMD) from 1968 to 2015. The CTMD archive is among the largest collections of video, sound recordings, photographs, and ephemera documenting the diversity of New York's immigrant performing arts traditions over the past fifty years. The collection includes hundreds of hours of audio and video recordings, newsletters, fliers, and photographs documenting music and dance of Balkan, Greek, Jewish, Irish American, Puerto Rican, Central Asian, South Asian, Haitian, Chinese, Korean, and other immigrant and ethnic communities including interviews and performances of more than 15 NEA National Heritage Award recipients.
Provenance
Center for Traditional Music and Dance; 2014.
Accruals
Further accruals are expected.
Access and Restrictions
The Center for Traditional Music and Dance collection is open to research. To request materials, please contact the Folklife Reading Room at https://hdl.loc.gov/loc.afc/folklife.contact
Certain restrictions to use or copying of materials may apply.
Biographical Note
The Center for Traditional Music and Dance (CTMD) was founded by Martin Koenig as the Balkan Arts Center in 1968. Together with Ethel Raim, Koenig guided its transformation into first, the Ethnic Arts Center in 1981 and then, the Center for Traditional Music and Dance in 1997. The Center assists New York City's immigrant communities in preserving the vitality of their distinctive performing arts traditions and promotes cross-cultural understanding by sharing these art forms with audiences across the city.
Scope and Content
The collection consists of audio and visual recordings, photographs, posters, and handouts related to programming by the Center for Traditional Music and Dance (CTMD) from 1968 to 2015. CTMD promotes and facilitates traditional immigrant and ethnic performing arts in the New York City metropolitan area. The CTMD collection is among the largest collections of video, sound recordings, photographs, and ephemera documenting the diversity of New York’s immigrant performing arts traditions over the past fifty years. The collection comprises both field recordings and program documentation.
Documentation from the 1970s focuses primarily on communities from the Balkans, Eastern and Southern Europe, including home audio recordings made by tamburitza musician George Skrbina, production material for the 1977 film The Popovich Brothers of South Chicago, and a series of field recordings of Bulgarian songs made by Martha Forsyth, 1980-1981.
Documentation from the 1980s and 1990s expands to include Center-produced recordings of Greek, Jewish, Irish American and Puerto Rican music, as well as its album of the Bukharan (Central Asian) Jewish ensemble, Shashmaqam, on the Smithsonian Folkways label. In addition, the Rhythms of New York concert series and associated video productions are included.
The collection also includes rare recordings of icons in folk and traditional performing arts, including more than fifteen NEA National Heritage Award recipients. These include: Puerto Rican bomba and plena master Juan Gutierrez and his ensemble, Los Pleneros de la 21; Greek lyra (fiddle) master Ilias Kementzides; Klezmer musician Andy Statman; Irish step dancer Donny Golden; Irish musician Mick Moloney; Palestinian musician and composer Simon Shaheen; Chinese pipa (lute) player Liang-xing Tang; Bukharan Jewish singer Fatimah Kuinova; Southern Italian musicians Guiseppe and Raffaela DeFranco; Irish flute player Jack Coen; Serbian Tamburitza master Adam Popovich; Epirot Greek clarinet master Perikles Halkias; Irish American fiddler Martin Mulvihill; Klezmer clarinetist Dave Tarras; Bulgarian saxophonist Yuri Yunakov; and Yiddish singer Beyle Scheachter Gottesman.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged into two series: Series 1: Newsletters and Series 2: Event Documentation. The latter series includes documentation across several media generations. While the collection was under the care of the Center for Traditional Music and Dance, many original recordings were transferred to newer media carriers, usually multiple times. Therefore, for any one event, the user may see similarly labeled entries on open reel audio tape, DAT, CD, and digital files, for example. The association between such recordings may be inferred to show several migrations of preservation copies from one carrier/technology to another.
Selected Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the LC Catalog. They are grouped by name of person or organization, by subject or location, and by occupation and listed alphabetically.
People
Allen, Ray; Alpert, Michael; Ambegaokar, Anjani; Berberian, John; Bern, Alan, 1955-; Castillo, Pepe; Cemal, Kemani; Coen, Jack; Cohen, John, 1932-2019; Diabate, Mamadou, 1975-; Diabaté, Abdoulaye, 1955-; Dolan, Brendan; Fefita La Grande; Feldman, Walter; Golden, Donny; Golden, Eileen; González, Andy, 1951-2020; Greenman, Steven; Gutiérrez, Juan, 1951-; Gutkin, Lisa; Hakmoun, Hassan; Halili, Merita; Halkias, Periklis, 1908-2005; Hayre, Carlos; Hyseni, Raif; Kementzides, Ilias, 1926-2006; Ključo, Merima; Koenig, Martin; Kolcio, Katja Pylyshenko; Kouyate, Djimo; Kuinova, Fatima; Kytasty, Julian; Marković, Boban; Min, Xiao-fen; Moloney, Mick, 1944-2022; Mulvihill, Brendan, 1954-; Mulvihill, Martin, 1923-; Nahachewsky, Andriy; Popovich, Adam N.; Raim, Ethel; Reagon, Bernice Johnson, 1942-; Roussos, John; Rubin, Joel, 1955-; Rushefsky, Pete; Salina, Eva; Schaechter-Gottesman, Beyle; Shaheen, Simon; Singh, Pritha; Statman, Andy, 1950-; Strauss, Deborah; Sweet, Ralph; Tang, Liangxing; Tarras, Dave, 1897-1989; Waletzky, Josh; Wang, Guowei; Yunakov, Yuri, 1958-
Organizations
Center for Traditional Music and Dance (New York, N.Y.); Cheres (Musical group); Cherish the Ladies (Musical group); Explosion Norteña (Musical group); Green Fields of America (Musical group); Halkias Family Orchestra; Launeddas Ensemble; Libre (Musical group); McCollough Sons of Thunder (Musical group); Merveilles d'Afrique (Dance company); Music from China (Musical group); New Birth Brass Band; Pablo Mayor's Folklore Urbano Orchestra; Pleneros de la 21 (Musical group); Popovich Brothers; Radio Tarifa (Musical group); Sexteto Criollo Puertorriqueño; Shashmaqam (Musical group); Son de la Loma (Musical group); Son Primero (Musical group); Super Manden (Musical group); Viento de Agua (Musical group); Wretched Refuse String Band; Zlatne Uste Balkan Brass Band
Subjects
Folk dance music--New York (State)--New York.; Folk dance music--United States.; Folk dancing, Balkan--United States.; Folk dancing--New York (State)--New York.; Folk festivals--New York (State)--New York.
Container List
- Series 1: Newsletters, 1975-2003
  - Balkan Arts Traditions, 1975 (Box-folder 1/1)
  - Balkan Arts Traditions, 1977 (Box-folder 1/2)
  - Newsletters, 1981 (Box-folder 1/3-4)
  - Newsletters, 1982 (Box-folder 1/5-8)
  - Newsletters, 1983 (Box-folder 1/9-12)
  - Newsletters, 1984-1991 (Box-folder 1/13-20)
  - Newsletters, 1993-2003 (Box-folder 1/21-30)
- Series 2: Event documentation, 1968-2015
  - Events, 1968-1973
    - Nonesuch Recording Session, June 1968
      - Sound Recordings, 1968-06-21 to 1968-06-25
        - 1 sound disc (CD), RS 68-0621-0625-1,2,3 (Box 17)
        - 32 audio files (wav): digital., RS 68-0621-0625-3
        - 33 audio files (wav): digital., RS 68-0621-0625-3b_4_5
    - Bulgarian Festival, July 1968
      - Sound Recordings, 1968-07
        - 1 sound disc (CD), BAC 68-1a, 1b (Box 15)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), BAC 68-07xx-1cd (Box 15)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), BAC 68-07xx-2,3 (Box 15)
    - Field Recordings from Bulgaria, March 1970
      - Sound Recordings, 1970-03-16
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: BAC 70-0316_1; Note on media: Martin Koenig, field recording; radio program broadcast on WBAI (NYC)
        - 1 sound cassette (DAT; 60 min.), AFC 2014/044: BAC 70-0316_2; Note on media: Martin Koenig, field recording; radio program braodcast on WBAI [NYC] [April 1970?]
        - 1 sound disc (CD), BAC 70-0316-1; Note on media: Radio Program Broadcast on WBAI (NYC) (Box 15)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), BAC 70-0316-2; Note on media: Radio Program Broadcast on WBAI (NYC) (Box 15)
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., BAC_70-0316-1
        - 1 audio file (wav): digital., BAC_70-0316-2
    - Spring Folk Festival, 1970 to 1973
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials
        - 1 folder, 1970-04-23, Note on folder: Third Annual Spring Folk Festival (Box-folder 2/2)
        - 1 folder, 1971-04-25, Note on folder: Concert of Songs and Dances from the Balkans (Box-folder 2/4)
        - 1 folder, 1972, Note on folder: New York Spring Folk Festival (Box-folder 2/9)
        - 2 folders, 1973-03-31 (Box-folder 2/10-11)
      - Photographs, 1973-03-31
        - 1 folder (Box-folder 14/2)
      - Sound Recordings, 1971-04-22 to 1971-04-25
        - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., AFC 2014/044: SFF 72-0422_1; Note on media: Remote to Balkans; McMillan Theatre, Columbia University
        - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., AFC 2014/044: SFF 72-0422_a
        - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., AFC 2014/044: SFF 72-0422_b
        - 1 sound disc (CD), SFF 71-0423-25-1-TD (Box 17)
        - 20 audio files (wav): digital., SFF 71-0423-25--1 TD
    - Winter Folk Festival, 1971 to 1973
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials
        - 1 folder, 1971-12-10 (Box-folder 2/7)
        - 1 folder, 1973-12-08 (Box-folder 2/13)
      - Sound Recordings, 1971-12-11
        - 1 sound disc (CD), WFF 71-1211-1 CD; Note on media: Barnard College (Box 17)
        - 10 audio files (wav): digital., WFF 71-1211-1
    - Smithsonian Festival of American Folklife, 1971 to 1973
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, 1971-07-01
        - 1 folder (Box-folder 2/5)
      - Moving Images, 1973-07
        - 1 videocassette (DVCAM; 124 min.), AFC 2014/044: Box 1-982xx_1
        - 1 videoreel (60 min.): 7 in. (diameter), ½ in. (width), AFC 2014/044: 982xx_1; Note on media: tribute to the Tamburashi 1973
        - 1 videoreel (60 min.): 7 in. (diameter), ½ in. (width), AFC 2014/044: 984xx_1; Note on media: tribute to the Tamburashi 1973
        - 1 videoreel (30 min.): 5 in. (diameter), ½ in. (width), AFC 2014/044: FAF-73-07xx_1; Note on media: Gundinci Dances, Tamburachi Dances
    - Recording Session: Villages of Vrsac, Siskovski, Gundinci, and Novi Sad, June-July 1973
      - Sound Recordings, 1973-06-28 to 1973-07-25
        - 1 sound disc (CD), RS 73-0628-0705-11,12,13; Note on media: Vrsac, Siskovski, and Gundinci (Box 17)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), RS 73-0628-0705-7, 8; Note on media: Vrsac, Gundinci, Novi Sad R.O. (Box 17)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), RS 73-0628-0705-9, 10; Note on media: Gundinci, Siskovski, Vrsac (Box 17)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), RS 73-0628-0725-1, 2; Note on media: Vrasac Session (Box 17)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), RS 73-0628-0725-3, 4; Note on media: Villages of Gundinci & Siskovski (Box 17)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), RS 73-0628-0725-5, 6; Note on media: Villages of Siskovski & Vrsac (Box 17)
    - Popovich Brothers interview, July 1973
      - Moving Images, 1973-07
        - 1 videoreel (30 min.): 5 in. (diameter), ½ in. (width), AFC 2014/044: POP-73-07xx_1
        - 1 videoreel (30 min.): 5 in. (diameter), ½ in. (width), AFC 2014/044: POP-73-07xx_2
        - 1 videocassette (DVCAM; 94 min.), AFC 2014/044: POP 73-07xx_1-2 (Popovic); FAF 73.07xx-1 (Gundinci); Note on media: Popovich Interview; Gundinci
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., POP 73-07xx_1-2 (Popovic); FAF 73.07xx-1 (Gundinci)
    - Mid-Hudson Valley Fall Folk Festival / An Evening of Traditional Music from the Balkans, October-December 1973
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, 1973-10-13
        - 1 folder (Box-folder 2/12)
      - Photographs, 1973-10-13
        - 1 folder, Note on folder: Balkan Singing Workshop (Box-folder 14/2)
      - Moving Images, 1973-10-13 to 1973-12-07
        - 1 videocassette (DVCAM; 124 min.), AFC 2014/044: BAC 73-1207_2, BAC 73-1013_1and2; Note on media: Balkan dance
        - 1 videoreel (30 min.): 5 in. (diameter), ½ in. (width), AFC 2014/044: BAC 73.1013_1
        - 1 videoreel (60 min.): 7 in. (diameter), ½ in. (width), AFC 2014/044: BAC 73.1013_2
        - 1 video file (mp4): digital., BAC 73-1207_2, BAC 73-1013_1and2; Note on media: New Paltz
        - 1 videoreel (30 min.): 5 in. (diameter), ½ in. (width), AFC 2014/044: BAC-73-1207_2
    - Other events, 1968 to 1973
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials
        - 1 folder, ca. 1969-1972, Note on folder: An Evening of Songs and Dances from the Balkans (Box-folder 2/1)
        - 1 folder, ca. 1971-1973, Note on folder: Folk Dance Fridays (Box-folder 2/3)
        - 1 folder, 1971-10-29, BAC 71-1029; Note on folder: A Presentation of Music and Dances from the Balkans (Box-folder 2/6)
        - 1 folder, 1971-12-13, BAC 71-1213; Note on folder: Pece Atanasovski Workshops (Box-folder 2/8)
      - Sound Recordings
        - 1 sound disc (CD), 1971-12-19, BAC 71-1219-1; Note on media: Reel to Reel field recording - Church; Stara Pazova (Box 15)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), 1970 to 1976, SI-DPA-FAF xxxx; Note on media: Smithsonian Insitution: Serbian Music (Box 17)
  - Events, 1974
    - Spring Folk Festival, April 1974
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, 1974-04-15 to 1974-04-20
        - 1 folder, SFF 74-0415; Note on folder: Sixth Annual Spring Folk Festival (Box-folder 2/14)
        - 1 folder, SFF 74-0417; Note on folder: Yiddish Folklore Presentation/Spring Folk Festival (Box-folder 2/15)
        - 2 folders, SFF 74-0420; Note on folder: Sixth Annual Spring Folk Festival (Box-folder 2/16-17)
        - 1 oversize folder, Note on media: Yiddish Folklore Presentation (Container oversize folder 1)
      - Sound Recordings, 1974-04-15 to 1974-04-21
        - 1 sound reel: 7 in., AFC 2014/044: SFF 74-0415_21_1
        - 1 sound reel: 7 in., AFC 2014/044: SFF 74-0415_21_2
        - 1 sound reel: 7 in., AFC 2014/044: SFF 74-0415_21_3
        - 1 sound reel: 7 in., AFC 2014/044: SFF 74-0415_21_4
        - 1 sound reel: 7 in., AFC 2014/044: SFF 74-0415_21_5
        - 1 sound reel: 7 in., AFC 2014/044: SFF 74-0415_21_6
        - 1 sound tape reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: SFF 74-0415-21_1_dub
        - 1 sound tape reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: SFF 74-0415-21_2_dub
        - 1 sound tape reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: SFF 74-0415-21_3_dub
        - 1 sound tape reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: SFF 74-0415-21_4_dub
        - 16 audio files (wav): digital., SFF 74-0415-21-1_2_3a
        - 1 sound disc (CD), SFF 74-0415-21-1,2,3a (Box 17)
        - 19 audio files (wav): digital., SFF 74-0415-21-3b_4
        - 1 sound disc (CD), SFF 74-0415-21-3b,4,5 (Box 17)
      - Sound Recordings, 1974-05-08
        - 1 sound tape reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: SFF 74-0508_1_2a_dub
        - 1 sound tape reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: SFF 74-0508_2b_3_dub
    - Festival of American Folklife, July 1974
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, 1974-07-03
        - 1 folder (Box-folder 2/18)
    - Pontic Summer, August 1974
      - Sound Recordings, 1974-08-03
        - 1 sound reel: 7 in., AFC 2014/044: BAC 74-0803_1; Note on media: Kostikas Konstandinidis
        - 1 sound tape reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: BAC 74-0803_1a_dub
        - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., AFC 2014/044: BAC 74-0803_1b
        - 1 sound reel: 7 in., AFC 2014/044: BAC 74-0803_2; Note on media: Kostikas Konstandinidis, Stathis Karamanlidis, Christoforos Christoforidis
        - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., AFC 2014/044: BAC 74-0803_2a
        - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., AFC 2014/044: BAC 74-0803_2b
        - 1 sound reel: 7 in., AFC 2014/044: BAC 74-0803_3; Note on media: Kostikas Konstandinidis, Stathis Karamanlidis, Christoforos Christoforidis
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: BAC 74-0803_3_dub; Note on media: Stathis Karamanides, Cristoforos Christoforidis, Ioannis Kalpatsinidis
        - 1 sound reel: 7 in., AFC 2014/044: BAC 74-0803_4; Note on media: Ioannis Kalpatsinidis
        - 1 sound tape reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: BAC 74-0803_4_dub
        - 1 sound disc (CD), BAC 74-0803-1,2a; Note on media: Interview and songs with Kostakis Konstandindis. Tommy Toromanides is translating. Ethel Raim is interviewing along with Martin Koenig. Musicians came over as part of Smithsonian Folklife Festival. (Box 15)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), BAC 74-0803-2b,3 (Box 15)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), BAC 74-0803-4; Note on media: Interviews with, performances by: Ioannis Kalpatsinidis (Box 15)
        - 28 audio files (wav): digital., BAC74-0803-1_2a
        - 56 audio files (wav): digital., BAC 74 0803-2b_3
        - 13 audio files (wav): digital., BAC 74 0803-4
    - Winter Folk Festival, December 1974
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, 1974-12-06
        - 1 folder, Note on folder: Seventh Annual Winter Folk Festival (Box-folder 2/19)
      - Sound Recordings, 1974-12-07
        - 1 sound reel: 7 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 74-1207_1
        - 1 sound reel: 7 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 74-1207_2
        - 1 sound reel: 7 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 74-1207_3
        - 1 sound reel: 7 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 74-1207_4
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 74-1207_5; Note on media: Koenig
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 74-1207_6; Note on media: Koenig
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 74-1207_7; Note on media: Koenig
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 74-1207_8; Note on media: Koenig
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 74-1207-1 RD
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 74-1207-2 RD
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 74-1207-3 RD
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: WFF 74-1207-4 RD
        - 1 sound disc (CD), WFF 74-1207-5,6-TD (Box 17)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), WFF 74-1207-7,8-TD (Box 18)
        - 25 audio files (wav): digital., WFF74-1207-5_6-TD
    - Field Research - Thessaloniki Radio recordings, 1974
      - Sound Recordings
        - 1 sound disc (CD), FR 74-XXXX-1 (Box 16)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), FR 74-xxxx-2 (Box 16)
  - Events, 1975
    - Balkan Folk Dance Festival, February 1975
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, 1975-02-07
        - 1 folder, BAC 75-0207 (Box-folder 2/20)
    - Spring Folk Festival, May 1975
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, 1975-05-15
        - 1 folder, SFF 75-0515; Note on folder: Eighth Annual Spring Folk Festival (Box-folder 2/21)
      - Sound Recordings, 1975-05-17
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: SFF 75-0517_1; Note on media: Macedonian Folksong Workshop
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: SFF 75-0517_2
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: SFF 75-0517_3
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: SFF 75-0517_4
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: SFF 75-0517_5
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: SFF 75-0517_6
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: SFF 75-0517_7
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: SFF 75-0517_8
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: SFF 75-0517_9
        - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., AFC 2014/044: SFF 75-0517_10; Note on media: Macedonian Folksong Concert/Dance Party
        - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., AFC 2014/044: SFF 75-0517_11
        - 1 sound disc (CD), SFF 75-0517-2, 3 (Box 17)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), SFF 75-0517-4, 5 (Box 17)
        - 17 audio files (wav): digital., SFF75-0517-2_3
        - 31 audio file (wav): digital., SFF75-0517-4_5
    - Popovich Brothers, September 1975
      - Sound Recordings, 1975-09-12 to 1975-09-19
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: POP 75-0912_1; Note on media: home
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: POP 75-0912_2; Note on media: home
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: POP 75-0912_3; Note on media: home
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: POP 75-0913-1; Note on media: VFW upstairs
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: POP 75-0913_1_downstairs; Note on media: VFW downstairs
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: POP 75-0913_1_upstairs; Note on media: VFW upstairs
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: POP 75-0913_2_downstairs; Note on media: VFW downstairs
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: POP 75-0913_2_upstairs; Note on media: VFW upstairs
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: POP 75-0913_3_downstairs; Note on media: VFW downstairs
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: POP 75-0913_3_upstairs; Note on media: VFW upstairs
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: POP 75-0913_4_downstairs; Note on media: VFW downstairs
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: POP 75-0913_4_upstairs; Note on media: VFW upstairs
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: POP 75-0913_5_downstairs; Note on media: VFW downstairs
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: POP 75-0913_5_upstairs; Note on media: VFW upstairs
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: POP 75-0913_6_downstairs; Note on media: VFW downstairs
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: POP 75-0913_6_upstairs; Note on media: VFW upstairs
        - 14 audio files (wav): digital., POP 75-0913-1 & 2
        - 19 audio files (wav): digital., POP 75091301_2 DS
        - 1 sound disc (CD), POP 75-0913-1&2; Note on media: VFW Downstairs (Box 17)
        - 1 sound disc (CD), POP 75-0913-1&2; Note on media: VFW upstairs (Box 17)
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: POP 75-0913-2; Note on media: VFW upstairs
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: POP 75-0913-3; Note on media: VFW upstairs
        - 1 sound disc (CD), POP 75-0913-3&4; Note on media: VFW upstairs (Box 17)
        - 19 audio files (wav): digital., POP 75-0913-3_4
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: POP 75-0913-4; Note on media: VFW upstairs
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: POP 75-0913-5; Note on media: VFW upstairs
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: POP 75-0913-6; Note on media: VFW upstairs
        - 1 sound tape reel (polyester): 10 in., AFC 2014/044: BAC 75-0914; Note on media: David Jones; Blake Norton
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: POP 75-0914_11; Note on media: concert
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: POP 75-0914_12; Note on media: concert
        - 1 sound reel, 2 track; 10 in., AFC 2014/044: POP 75-0914_13; Note on media: banquet
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: POP 75-0914_14; Note on media: banquet
        - 1 sound reel: 10 in., AFC 2014/044: POP 75-0914_15; Note on media: banquet
        - 1 sound disc (CD), POP 75-0914-11,12; Note on media: Concert and awards (Box 17)
        - 18 audio files (wav): digital., POP 750914-11_12 Concert